<?xml version="1.0"?>
<characters>
	<Superman>
		<image>http://images2.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20100419210631/marvel_dc/images/thumb/1/14/Superman_0002.jpg/320px-Superman_0002.jpg</image>
		<text>Superman is the most powerful being on planet Earth, an alien immigrant named Kal-El from the planet Krypton who was raised in Smallville, Kansas, to become an American superhero. 
		Raised with high moral ideals, he uses his incredible strength, speed, flight and various other superpowers to fight evil and protect the innocent. In his civilian identity he is Clark Kent, 
		a mild-mannered reporter working for the Daily Planet in Metropolis. He is a founding member of the Justice League of America and a charter member of the Legion of Super-Heroes in the 30th Century.
		Superman was created by Jerry Siegel and Joe Shuster in 1938, first appearing in Action Comics #1. 
		</text>
	</Superman>
	<Wonder_Woman>
		<image>http://images1.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20130322192444/marvel_dc/images/thumb/3/3b/Wonder_Woman_Vol_4_18_Textless.jpg/308px-Wonder_Woman_Vol_4_18_Textless.jpg</image>
		<text>Wonder Woman is the Amazonian princess Diana; the daughter of the Amazonian Queen Hippolyta and the Olympian god Zeus. While the Amazons traditionally procreated by raping and then murdering sailors who 
		happened too close to their island, Hippolyta was supposed to have been barren. Legend told that Diana was born of her mother's strong desire for a child, a lump of clay brought to life in the form of a girl; 
		the perfect Amazon, as she was born of no man. The truth, though, was that Hippolyta had had an affair with Zeus, and Diana's real parentage was hidden in order to protect the Queen and her daughter from the wrath of 
		Zeus' notoriously jealous wife Hera. As such, Diana's power was inherited through her divine blood. Wonder Woman was created by William Moulton Marston and Harry G. Peter, first appearing in All-Star Comics #8. (1941) 
		</text>
	</Wonder_Woman>
	<Batman>
		<image>http://images2.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20120228075315/marvel_dc/images/thumb/5/5e/Batman_0683.jpg/315px-Batman_0683.jpg</image>
		<text>Batman is the superhero protector of Gotham City, a man dressed like a bat who fights against evil and strikes terror into the hearts of criminals everywhere. In his secret identity he is Bruce Wayne, 
		billionaire industrialist and notorious playboy. Although he has no superhuman powers, he is one of the world's smartest men and greatest fighters. His physical prowess and technical ingenuity make him an incredibly 
		dangerous opponent. He is also a founding member of the Justice League and the Outsiders. Batman was created by Bob Kane and Bill Finger, first appearing in Detective Comics #27. (1939) 
		</text>
	</Batman>
	<Zatanna>
		<image>http://images3.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20111228170902/marvel_dc/images/thumb/e/ea/Justice_League_Dark_0006.jpg/339px-Justice_League_Dark_0006.jpg</image>
		<text> Zatanna is a superhero and one of the greatest magic-users in the DC Universe. Her father is the legendary magician Zatara and she works hard to live up to his legacy. The traditional method of spell-casting 
		she uses involves speaking words and sentences backwards. In addition to her career as a hero, she is also a very notable stage performer. She has been a member of the Justice League of America, the Sentinels of Magic, 
		and the Seven Soldiers. Zatanna was created by Gardner Fox and Murphy Anderson, first appearing in Hawkman #4. (1964)  
		</text>
	</Zatanna>
	<General_Zod>
		<image>http://images2.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20130911171245/marvel_dc/images/thumb/0/0a/Action_Comics_Vol_2_23.2_Zod_Textless.jpg/351px-Action_Comics_Vol_2_23.2_Zod_Textless.jpg</image>
		<text> General Zod is a former Kryptonian military general and an enemy to Superman. Exiled to the Phantom Zone by his people for treason, he survived the destruction of Krypton and swore revenge against the 
		son of Jor-El. He is a member of the Kryptonian Military Guild and the Phantom Zoners. General Zod was created by Robert Bernstein and George Papp, first appearing in Adventure Comics #283. (1961) </text>
	</General_Zod>
	<Blackfire>
		<image>http://images1.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20121017215211/marvel_dc/images/thumb/7/70/Red_Hood_and_the_Outlaws_Vol_1_13_Textless.jpg/316px-Red_Hood_and_the_Outlaws_Vol_1_13_Textless.jpg</image>
		<text>Blackfire is a Tamaranean super-villain and enemy to the Teen Titans. Born to the royal family of Tamaran, her brother is Darkfire and her sister is Starfire. Despite being the eldest child, her subjects hated 
		her and the birthright was passed to Starfire because of this. This made her hate her sister, and she was disgraced from the family after trying to murder her. Joining the Citadel empire, she betrayed her people and 
		helped the invaders subjugate them. Blackfire was created by Marv Wolfman and George Perez, first appearing in New Teen Titans #22. (1982) 
		</text>
	</Blackfire>
	<The_Joker>
		<image>http://images4.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20080825194351/marvel_dc/images/thumb/5/58/Joker_0003.jpg/320px-Joker_0003.jpg</image>
		<text>The Joker is a serial killer and a super-villain, a dangerous madman who dresses like a clown and commits violent crimes. He is often recognized as Batman's greatest enemy, living in and terrorizing Gotham City, 
		although he spends most of his time in Arkham Asylum. In addition to being a deadly and unpredictable physical combatant, he is a brilliant and ruthless criminal mastermind. His crimes require no motivation other than 
		his sadistic desire to show people the meaninglessness of life through pain and death, and the narcissism to see the world remade in his own image. He is constantly adapting his personality and his psychosis to respond 
		to the world around him, sometimes a harmless trickster and at others a brutal mass-murderer. Batman is his only worthy opponent, and although he has passed up multiple opportunities to murder the dark knight, he has 
		no such problems with killing Robin or crippling Batgirl. Although his origins remain unclear and shrouded in mystery, it is also known that prior to the chemical accident that scarred his mind and body he was the 
		small-time criminal Red Hood. He has also been a member of the Injustice Gang and the Injustice League. Joker was created by Jerry Robinson, Bill Finger and Bob Kane, first appearing in Batman #1. (1940)
		</text>
	</The_Joker>
	<Harley_Quinn>
		<image>http://images2.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20130525171714/marvel_dc/images/thumb/e/e3/Suicide_Squad_Vol_4_6_Textless.jpg/310px-Suicide_Squad_Vol_4_6_Textless.jpg</image>
		<text>Harley Quinn is a flamboyant super-villain and an adversary of Batman usually recognized as the Joker's girlfriend, although she has had her own strong solo career. Born Harleen Quinzel, she had been working as 
		a psychologist at Arkham Asylum where she was assigned to the Joker and fell in love with him. This led to her adopting her own costumed persona, adapting the word harlequin, to assist him escape and cause further 
		mayhem. Their relationship is passionate and continuously off-on, with Harley's best friend Poison Ivy constantly encouraging her to break up with for good. However, Harley's love for the Joker eventually brings her 
		back to his side with the Joker himself demonstrating a keen need for her despite himself. When not with the Joker, she has been working mostly on her own in Gotham City, sometimes teaming up with her other friends. 
		Her special abilities include an enhanced physiology due to chemical experimentation, giving her increased strength, agility and durability. She has been a member of the Secret Society of Super-Villains, the Secret Six 
		and the Gotham City Sirens. Harley Quinn was originally created by Paul Dini and Bruce Timm as a character in the DCAU. Her first appearance was in the Batman: The Animated Series episode "Joker's Favor." (1992) Several 
		years later, her first appearance in regular continuity took place in the graphic novel Batman: Harley Quinn. (1999)
		</text>
	</Harley_Quinn>
	<Doctor_Strange>
		<image>http://images2.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20121128191061/marveldatabase/images/thumb/4/45/Stephen_Strange_%28Earth-616%29_from_New_Avengers_Vol_2_34.jpg/213px-Stephen_Strange_%28Earth-616%29_from_New_Avengers_Vol_2_34.jpg</image>
		<text>Doctor Stephen Vincent Strange (known as Doctor Strange) is a fictional character, a superhero that appears in comic books published by Marvel Comics. Doctor Strange is a former neurosurgeon, a practicing sorcerer, 
		and serves as the Sorcerer Supreme — the primary protector of Earth against magical and mystical threats. Co-created by writer-editor Stan Lee and artist/co-plotter Steve Ditko, the character debuted 
		in Strange Tales #110 (July 1963)
		</text>
	</Doctor_Strange>
	<Storm>
		<image>http://images4.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20130123034515/marveldatabase/images/7/76/Ororo_Munroe_%28Earth-616%29_from_Uncanny_X-Force_Vol_2_1.png</image>
		<text>After her parents were murdered in the rubble of a plane crash, Ororo Munro began life as a thief with a severe case of claustrophobia, until she was worshiped as a goddess in a tribe in Africa. After Professor 
		Charles Xavier recruited her for his X-Men, Ororo matured to the point of leading them, fighting for the peaceful coexistence of mutants and humans most of her life. She's been the object of many powerful men's 
		obsession including Black Panther, Arkon the Imperion, Dracula, and Dr. Doom. Splitting leadership with Cyclops, Ororo eventually formed the splinter group, X-Treme X-Men, while searching for the future-telling 
		Destiny's diaries. After receiving government sanction for her team, becoming the X-Treme Sanctions Executive, Storm eventually came to be Queen of Wakanda for a time, by way of marrying the Black Panther, but her 
		marriaged ended during the Avengers vs X-Men conflict. With her mutant power to manipulate the forces that govern weather, enabling her to summon wind, rain, sleet, snow, and even lightning at will, Storm is the 
		Headmistress of the Jean Grey School and remains a stalwart veteran X-Man. Storm first appeared in 1975 in Giant-Size X-Men #1, written by Len Wein and pencilled by Dave Cockrum.
		</text>
	</Storm>
	<Deadpool>
		<image>http://images1.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20130813233202/marveldatabase/images/thumb/a/a4/Wade_Wilson_%28Earth-616%29_from_X-Men_Battle_of_the_Atom_Vol_1_1_cover.jpg/252px-Wade_Wilson_%28Earth-616%29_from_X-Men_Battle_of_the_Atom_Vol_1_1_cover.jpg</image>
		<text>Wade Wilson was an international assassin who had worked for various governments when he developed cancer. In an effort to find a cure, he enrolled in the Weapon X program in Canada, which gave him a healing 
		factor from another member and set him to work for them. When he killed a team member, he was thrown out of the program and was sent to have his abilities removed, where he was experimented on instead. The results 
		of his stay there were a diminished mental state, a healing factor that could not cure his cancer or heal his scars, in infatuation with death, and his freedom to return to for-hire mercenary work. As "The Merc with 
		a Mouth" he set out as Deadpool to kill and have a good time doing it. Created by artist Rob Liefeld and writer Fabian Nicieza, Deadpool made his first appearance in the pages of New Mutants #98 published in February 1991.
		</text>
	</Deadpool>
	<Jubilee>
		<image>http://images2.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20131016151352/marveldatabase/images/thumb/8/8f/Jubilee_%28Earth-616%29.002.jpg/184px-Jubilee_%28Earth-616%29.002.jpg</image>
		<text>A mutant, Jubilation "Jubilee" Lee had the superhuman power to generate "sparkles" out of her hands, consisting of explosive plasma. A teenage "mall rat," she was the X-Men's youngest member in the early 1990s, 
		often playing sidekick to Wolverine. She eventually joined the junior team Generation X. Jubilee has since gained the powers of a vampire from her transformation by the bite of Xarus, son of Dracula. Her powers 
		include superhuman strength and speed, and the ability to turn into vapor. It is possible that she can heal much faster than a human. As a vampire, Jubilee now possesses all of the weaknesses of a vampire. She must 
		sustain herself on blood and avoid direct sunlight, garlic, silver, and religious symbols. Jubilee was created by writer Chris Claremont and artist Marc Silvestri and first appeared in Uncanny X-Men #244 (May 1989).
		</text>
	</Jubilee>
	<Magneto>
		<image>http://images4.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20130215204031/marveldatabase/images/thumb/0/0a/Max_Eisenhardt_%28Earth-616%29_from_Uncanny_X-Men_Vol_3_3_002.jpg/252px-Max_Eisenhardt_%28Earth-616%29_from_Uncanny_X-Men_Vol_3_3_002.jpg</image>
		<text>Magneto (born Max Eisenhardt) was a German Jew in Auschwitz Concentration Camp, his experiences there were the basis of his action in the decades to follow. He was a friend of Charles Xavier (around that time he 
		discovered his mutant magnetism power) who would later become the founder of the X-Men, but parted ways due to their ideologies being too different. Some time later he formed the Brotherhood of Mutants as a mutant 
		supremacy group which came into conflict with the X-Men a number of times, but has sometimes fought alongside them against a greater threat. Magneto is, as his name of choice implies, truly a master of magnetism. He can 
		control all forms of magnetism, both artificial and natural. It is unclear, however, if he is able to draw magnetic force from outside himself, in which case he would be able to manipulate it over vast distances, or if 
		he draws it from within himself. It is also unclear if his powers are psionic in nature, or purely physiological. It is possible that he merely focuses his power through his body. His power is, for all practical intents, 
		boundless. He can even achieve certain tasks with his power simultaneously, such as completely assembling a complicated machine within seconds, and erecting a field of nearly impenetrable magnetic energy to protect 
		himself from harm. Magneto was created by writer Stan Lee and artist Jack Kirby, and first appeared in the debut issue of X-Men in 1963.</text>
	</Magneto>
	<Shriek>
		<image>http://images3.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20060322200638/marveldatabase/images/thumb/e/e8/Frances_Barrison_%28Earth-616%29_0001.jpg/183px-Frances_Barrison_%28Earth-616%29_0001.jpg</image>
		<text>Shriek is a dangerous and criminally insane villainess with the ability to manipulate sound. During the events of Maximum Carnage, she allied herself with Carnage and several other supervillains who went about 
		New York on a killing spree. Shriek's origins and real name are uncertain. She was named Sandra Deel in her earliest appearances, but named Frances Louise Barrison in later appearances. Shriek has the ability to manipulate 
		sound in a number of elaborate ways. She can harness it for destructive concussive force or use it to disorient and agitate her enemies. She can apparently hypersonically induce intense emotion in those around her 
		(generating fear, hate, or despair). She also has moderate powers of levitation that she can use to make herself fly and possibly some low level of psionic ability. She is able to sense the darkest side to a person's psyche 
		so that she can use her powers to specifically manipulate that person's emotions. Her scarred left eye is also prone to glow whenever she uses her powers. Why only that eye glows is uncertain. She was created by Tom DeFalco, 
		Mike W. Barr, Terry Kavanagh, Ron Lim, Jerry Bingham, and Mark Bagley and first appeared in Spider-Man Unlimited volume 1 #1 (May 1993).</text>
	</Shriek>
	<Loki>
		<image>http://images4.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20121027120555/marveldatabase/images/thumb/0/01/Journey_into_Mystery_645_textless.jpg/303px-Journey_into_Mystery_645_textless.jpg</image>
		<text>Loki is one of several powerful beings from the magical realm of Asgard, who have been worshipped as gods. Odin, once the ruler of the Asgardian gods, led his subjects in a war against their enemy, the frost 
		giants from the land of Jotunheim (one of the nine worlds of Asgard). Laufey, king of the frost giants, was slain in battle and the giants were defeated. Surveying the spoils of war, the Asgardians discovered a small 
		Asgardian god-sized baby hidden at the giants' main fortress. The infant was Loki, whom Laufey had kept hidden due to his shame over his son's diminutive size. Odin remembered his father Bor’s dying words to adopt the 
		son of a father killed by his hands; Odin adopted Loki into his own family, raising Loki like a son along with his biological son, Thor. He possesses physical attributes equal to a fit average member of the race of superbeings, 
		the Asgardians, such as enhanced strength; stamina, speed, durability, (his Frost Giant metabolism grants him superhuman levels of physical stamina in practically all activities); durability enough to harmlessly withstand 
		high-caliber bullets; and immunity to all known diseases and toxins, as well as some resistance to magic.b Loki is of genius level intelligence and has extensive training in magic, and possesses the ability to manipulate 
		magical forces for a variety of purposes: energy projection, creation of force fields, temporarily increasing his own physical strength, granting superhuman abilities to living beings or inanimate objects, flight, 
		hypnosis, illusion casting, and inter-dimensional teleportation. Loki made his first Marvel Comics appearance in Timely Comics' publication Venus #6 (August 1949).
		</text>
	</Loki>
	<Mystique>
		<image>http://images1.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20130611014840/marveldatabase/images/thumb/1/15/Raven_Darkholme_%28Earth-616%29_from_All-New_X-Men_Vol_1_7_001.png/161px-Raven_Darkholme_%28Earth-616%29_from_All-New_X-Men_Vol_1_7_001.png</image>
		<text>Raven Darkholme, otherwise known as Mystique, has a very convoluted history about which very little is known, the exception being that she is over a century old and was most likely born somewhere in Austria. 
		Mystique is a mutant shapeshifter with the ability to psionically shift the formation of her biological cells at will to change her appearance and thereby assume the form of other humans. She can also alter her 
		voice to duplicate exactly that of another person. Originally, it was clearly stated that Mystique's powers were limited to appearances only; she could not assume the powers of the people she morphed into or 
		alter her body to adapt to different situations. Additionally she could not change her overall body mass when taking on the appearance of a person larger or smaller, but thanks to subsequent enhancements she has 
		stated that her body mass is not fixed and can change when she does. She is the biological mother of both Nightcrawler and Graydon Creed, whose father was the mutant Sabretooth. Ironically, Graydon turned out 
		to be just a normal human and became the mutant-hating leader of the racist group known as the Friends of Humanity. He was eventually assassinated by Mystique herself. Her third child, by adoption, was Rogue, 
		who would eventually join the X-Men after turning her back on Mystique's Brotherhood Of Evil Mutants. Mystique was created by artist David Cockrum, and first appeared in Ms. Marvel No.16 (May 1978).
		</text>
	</Mystique>
</characters>